Probo Krishnacahya

Frontend Developer & UI/UX Designer

™ probo.krishnacahya@gmail.com in Probo Krishnacahya

★ https://probo-krishnacahya.web.app/



About Me

I am proficient in Frontend Development and UI/UX Design with 2+ years of experience to create interactive and aesthetic visual designs while still prioritizing ease of use and accessibility so as to produce a satisfying user experience. Along with that, Cooperative Teamwork, Proactive, Persistence, Lifelong Learner, and High Sense of Achievement are the key points that define me.

Professional Experience

Tech (Coder) Intern at Apple Developer Academy @ UC Cohort 2023

Apple Developer Academy @ UC

March 2023 - present

Student Assistant

Universitas Ciputra Surabaya ∂ February 2023 – present

Lecturer Research Assistant

Universitas Ciputra Surabaya ∂ August 2022 - January 2023

Educations

Universitas Ciputra Surabaya 🔗

Sarjana Komputer, Informatika 2020 – 2024

Sekolah Menengah Atas Kristen Dharma Mulya Surabaya ∂

Ilmu Pengetahuan Sosial 2017 – 2020

☆ Skills

SwiftUI	• • • • •
ReactJS	• • • • •
Flutter	• • • • •
Bootstrap	• • • • •
Figma	• • • • •

₩ Languages		
Indonesian		
English		
Chinese		

Awards

2nd Place in Lomba Nasional Kreativitas Mahasiswa 2022 ∂

Asosiasi Perguruan Tinggi Swasta Indonesia Wilayah VII Jawa Timur November 2022

Web/Mobile Application Category

2nd Place in National Informatic Fun Competition 2K22 ∂

Universitas Muhammadiyah Riau August 2022 UI/UX Design Category

9th Place in Faculty of Information Technology Competition 2022 Ø

Universitas Kristen Satya Wacana Salatiga August 2022 Web Developer Category

战 Volunteering

Bebras Indonesia Computational Thinking Challenge 2022 ∅

Member of UC Bureau Committee November 2022 – January 2023

Best Practices on Computational Thinking for Future Educators Workshop *∂*

Member of Module (Presentation Slides) Division July 2022 – September 2022

Technopreneurship Workshop $\mathscr D$

Member of IT - Inventory Division April 2022

8th National Programming & Logic Competition §

Member of Marketing Division November 2020 – January 2021